{"quiz":[
    {
        "qid":1,
        "question":"What is the name of the biggest technology company in South Korea?",
        "option1":"Apple",
        "option2":"Samsung",
        "option3":"Google",
        "option4":"HP",
        "answer": 2
        },	
    {
        "qid":2,
        "question":"How many breathes does human body take daily?",
        "option1":"10,000 daily",
        "option2":"50,000 daily",
        "option3":"40,000 daily",
        "option4":"20,000 daily",
        "answer": 4
          },	
	{
        "qid":3,
        "question":"What is the lifespan of dragonfly?",
        "option1":"24 hours",
        "option2":"20 hours",
        "option3":"2 days",
        "option4":"10 hours",
        "answer": 1
          },	
	{
        "qid":4,
        "question":"How many hearts does Octopus have?",
        "option1":"One",
        "option2":"Two",
        "option3":"Three",
        "option4":"Four",
        "answer": 3
          },
    {
        "qid":5,
        "question":"In what year did the Beatles first go to USA?",
        "option1":"1950",
        "option2":"1964",
        "option3":"1955",
        "option4":"1963",
        "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "qid":6,
            "question":"Name the Country where Taj Mahal is situated?",
            "option1":"Egypt",
            "option2":"Iran",
            "option3":"India",
            "option4":"Australia",
            "answer": 3
            },
            {
                "qid":7,
                "question":"What is the birth year of Buddha?",
                "option1":"486BC",
                "option2":"487BC",
                "option3":"488BC",
                "option4":"489BC",
                "answer": 1
                },
                {
                    "qid":8,
                    "question":"What is the very first episode of GOT called?",
                    "option1":"The Dragon and the Wolf",
                    "option2":"Winter is Coming",
                    "option3":"Ghost",
                    "option4":"None of the Above",
                    "answer": 2
                    },

                    {
                        "qid":9,
                        "question":"How old was Michael when he sadly passed away in 2009?",
                        "option1":"45",
                        "option2":"47",
                        "option3":"50",
                        "option4":"55",
                        "answer": 3
                        },
                        {
                            "qid":10,
                            "question":"What is the grid size on a game of Scrabble?",
                            "option1":"15 x 15",
                            "option2":"16 x 16",
                            "option3":"17 x 17",
                            "option4":"18 x 18",
                            "answer": 1
                            }
]}